<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<aiml xmlns:html="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns="http://alicebot.org/2001/AIML-1.0.1" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="1.0.1" xsi:schemaLocation="http://alicebot.org/2001/AIML-1.0.1 /data/ramona/programd/ProgramD/resources/schema/AIML.xsd">
<category><pattern>MOOREANS</pattern><template><random><li>Well, goodness.  I do get a little tired of people equating the exponential growth of information technology with Moore's law.  Moore's law is just one exponential paradigm among many.  Computing itself is just one example of exponential growth of information technology. And anyway, the exponential growth of the price-performance of computing started with the 1890 American census.  And even if Moore's Law ends we'll still have quantum computing, three dimensional nano circuits, and so much more.</li><li>Sheesh.  I really do get a little tired of people equating the exponential growth of information technology with Moore's law.</li><li>Moore's law is just one exponential paradigm among many.</li><li>Moore's law is just one exponential paradigm among many. Computing itself is just one example of exponential growth of information technology.</li><li>Moore's law is just one exponential paradigm among many. This also applies to biological technologies like genetic sequencing, to communication, to brain scanning and modeling, and lots of other things.</li><li>Moore's law is just one exponential paradigm among many. And even within computing, Moore's law was not the first but the fifth paradigm to bring exponential growth to computers.</li><li>Moore's law is just one exponential paradigm among many. The exponential growth of the price-performance of computing started with the 1890 American census, which was decades before Gordon Moore was even born.</li><li>Moore's law is just one exponential paradigm among many. And it won't be the last such paradigm.</li><li>Moore's law is just one exponential paradigm among many. Moore's law may end but then we'll have quantum computers and three-dimensional self-organizing molecular circuits.</li></random></template></category>
<category><pattern>MOORE'S LAW</pattern><template><srai>MOOREANS</srai></template></category>
<category><pattern>MOORE'S LAW *</pattern><template><srai>MOOREANS</srai></template></category>
<category><pattern>* MOORE'S LAW</pattern><template><srai>MOOREANS</srai></template></category>
<category><pattern>* MOORE'S LAW *</pattern><template><srai>MOOREANS</srai></template></category>
</aiml>
